Goal

Creative designer with 2+ years' experience in communicating effectively with designs and photography. One to create highly conceptual concepts and ideas that will effectively communicate to desired target markets to achieve desired results. Adept with the following design platforms: **Photoshop, Indesign, Bridge, Illustrator, Acrobat, Lightroom,** and **Maya 3D.** Through these mediums I can provide you image manipulaton, branding, collateral design, logos, editorials, and ideas. I can also provide your entity my skills in flash photography which include portraiture, product, event, nightlife, and architecture. I can solve your problems effectively with in depth knowledge of working with advanced photography equipment, programs, and physical tools.

Expertise:

- Photography and retouching Creative problem solving Lens adjustment Image manipulation Flash equipment
- Basic web design Adobe Suite & Autodesk Image processing Branding Logo Design Having charisma and personality

Experience:

Eye Urban Television - February 2012 - June 2013 Camera Operator

- Deliver realistic, high quality images and videos as assignments dictated.
- Edit and retouch images as needed.
- Communicate with clients to decipher project needs.
- Planned with producers to ensure management of all photography assignmentsv

MyBeatFix - January 2014 - January 2015 Photo Journalist / Graphic Designer

- Published photos periodically to social media sites which resulted in increased web presence.
- Produced video for WMC (winter music conference)
- Retouch and edit images as needed.
- Ensure appropriate photo quality.
- Represented company and managed event coverage.
- Created graphics to market events via social media.

FDR/Treehouse nightclub - August 2014 - currently contracted Event Photographer

- Produced realistic and creative images for company social media.
- Communicate event guest where to find photos.
- Reotuch and color corrected photos.

District Creative Studios - May 2014 - Currently interning Graphic Design/Photographer

- \bullet Created graphics for new clothing line.
- Produced photo shoots for company.
- \bullet Retouch photos and manipulated images to incorporated apparel graphics.
- Oversaw projects of other designers.

IpaddleMiami LLC - May 2014 - Current client Cheif Graphic Designer

- Branded entire company.
- Logo design, and apparel design.
- Designed all collateral for print, and digital mediums.

Dark Matter Collective - Independent contractor Graphic Designer

- Work cohesively with strong team to create solutions for clients
- Work dillegently to provide client with solutions.
- Design every aspect of clients entitiy which includes: digital media, collateral, brand, and etc.

Education

Miami Dade College Wolfson - Transferred Miami int'l university - Currently enrolled

Bachelors degree in Graphic Design - September 2013 to September 2016

GPA: 3.6

Photographer and designer for school newspaper and multiple club organizations.

Member of AIGA